{
  "beginner": [
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'raisin'?",
      "choices": [
        "grape",
        "apple",
        "banana",
        "fig"
      ],
      "answer": "grape",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'mangue'?",
      "choices": [
        "mango",
        "papaya",
        "melon",
        "peach"
      ],
      "answer": "mango",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'framboise'?",
      "choices": [
        "raspberry",
        "strawberry",
        "blackberry",
        "currant"
      ],
      "answer": "raspberry",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'framboise'?",
      "choices": [
        "raspberry",
        "strawberry",
        "blackberry",
        "currant"
      ],
      "answer": "raspberry",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'tomate'?",
      "choices": [
        "tomato",
        "pepper",
        "lettuce",
        "onion"
      ],
      "answer": "tomato",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'oignon'?",
      "choices": [
        "onion",
        "garlic",
        "leek",
        "shallot"
      ],
      "answer": "onion",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'main'?",
      "choices": [
        "hand",
        "arm",
        "leg",
        "foot"
      ],
      "answer": "hand",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'bras'?",
      "choices": [
        "arm",
        "hand",
        "shoulder",
        "elbow"
      ],
      "answer": "arm",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'doigt'?",
      "choices": [
        "finger",
        "toe",
        "nail",
        "hand"
      ],
      "answer": "finger",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for ''?",
      "choices": [
        "skin",
        "hair",
        "nails",
        "toes"
      ],
      "answer": "skin",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pied'?",
      "choices": [
        "foot",
        "hand",
        "toe",
        "knee"
      ],
      "answer": "foot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'bouche'?",
      "choices": [
        "mouth",
        "tongue",
        "cheek",
        "lip"
      ],
      "answer": "mouth",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'doigt'?",
      "choices": [
        "finger",
        "toe",
        "hand",
        "thumb"
      ],
      "answer": "finger",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chat'?",
      "choices": [
        "cat",
        "dog",
        "house",
        "bird"
      ],
      "answer": "cat",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'merci'?",
      "choices": [
        "thank you",
        "sorry",
        "excuse me",
        "yes"
      ],
      "answer": "thank you",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '\u00e9cole'?",
      "choices": [
        "school",
        "university",
        "classroom",
        "teacher"
      ],
      "answer": "school",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'vacances'?",
      "choices": [
        "holiday",
        "journey",
        "trip",
        "rest"
      ],
      "answer": "holiday",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'confiance'?",
      "choices": [
        "hope",
        "trust",
        "confidence",
        "power"
      ],
      "answer": "confidence",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chemise'?",
      "choices": [
        "shirt",
        "pants",
        "jacket",
        "hat"
      ],
      "answer": "shirt",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chapeau'?",
      "choices": [
        "hat",
        "belt",
        "coat",
        "sock"
      ],
      "answer": "hat",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'robe'?",
      "choices": [
        "dress",
        "coat",
        "jacket",
        "blouse"
      ],
      "answer": "dress",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'manteau'?",
      "choices": [
        "coat",
        "shirt",
        "hoodie",
        "jacket"
      ],
      "answer": "coat",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for ''?",
      "choices": [
        "raincoat",
        "hoodie",
        "sweater",
        "vest"
      ],
      "answer": "raincoat",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'professeur'?",
      "choices": [
        "teacher",
        "principal",
        "student",
        "friend"
      ],
      "answer": "teacher",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'stylo'?",
      "choices": [
        "pen",
        "pencil",
        "ruler",
        "marker"
      ],
      "answer": "pen",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'emploi du temps'?",
      "choices": [
        "schedule",
        "diary",
        "report",
        "syllabus"
      ],
      "answer": "schedule",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'melancholy'?",
      "choices": [
        "sadness",
        "joy",
        "fear",
        "anger"
      ],
      "answer": "sadness",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'abricot'?",
      "choices": [
        "apricot",
        "plum",
        "peach",
        "pear"
      ],
      "answer": "apricot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'abricot'?",
      "choices": [
        "apricot",
        "plum",
        "peach",
        "pear"
      ],
      "answer": "apricot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pomme'?",
      "choices": [
        "apple",
        "banana",
        "grape",
        "kiwi"
      ],
      "answer": "apple",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'avocat'?",
      "choices": [
        "avocado",
        "banana",
        "lime",
        "papaya"
      ],
      "answer": "avocado",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pomme de terre'?",
      "choices": [
        "potato",
        "carrot",
        "beet",
        "pea"
      ],
      "answer": "potato",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'carotte'?",
      "choices": [
        "carrot",
        "parsnip",
        "zucchini",
        "turnip"
      ],
      "answer": "carrot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ananas'?",
      "choices": [
        "pineapple",
        "pinapple",
        "pineappel",
        "pineaple"
      ],
      "answer": "pineapple",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'fraise'?",
      "choices": [
        "strawberry",
        "strawbery",
        "strawbary",
        "strowberry"
      ],
      "answer": "strawberry",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'brocoli'?",
      "choices": [
        "broccoli",
        "brocoly",
        "brokoli",
        "broccoly"
      ],
      "answer": "broccoli",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'betterave'?",
      "choices": [
        "beetroot",
        "beatroot",
        "beatroat",
        "bitroot"
      ],
      "answer": "beetroot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'champignon'?",
      "choices": [
        "mushroom",
        "mashroom",
        "muschroom",
        "mouchroom"
      ],
      "answer": "mushroom",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'persil'?",
      "choices": [
        "parsley",
        "parslay",
        "parsly",
        "parceley"
      ],
      "answer": "parsley",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'cheveux'?",
      "choices": [
        "hair",
        "hare",
        "hear",
        "herr"
      ],
      "answer": "hair",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'sourcil'?",
      "choices": [
        "eyebrow",
        "ankle",
        "knee",
        "heel"
      ],
      "answer": "eyebrow",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'genou'?",
      "choices": [
        "knee",
        "back",
        "head",
        "chest"
      ],
      "answer": "knee",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'yeux'?",
      "choices": [
        "eyes",
        "ears",
        "mouth",
        "skin"
      ],
      "answer": "eyes",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'genou'?",
      "choices": [
        "knee",
        "ankle",
        "heel",
        "toe"
      ],
      "answer": "knee",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'cheville'?",
      "choices": [
        "ankle",
        "heel",
        "knee",
        "calf"
      ],
      "answer": "ankle",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'poignet'?",
      "choices": [
        "wrist",
        "elbow",
        "hand",
        "palm"
      ],
      "answer": "wrist",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'coude'?",
      "choices": [
        "elbow",
        "wrist",
        "shoulder",
        "hand"
      ],
      "answer": "elbow",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pouce'?",
      "choices": [
        "thumb",
        "finger",
        "hand",
        "palm"
      ],
      "answer": "thumb",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'yeux'?",
      "choices": [
        "eye",
        "ear",
        "mouth",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "eye",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'avant bras'?",
      "choices": [
        "forearm",
        "hand",
        "bicep",
        "shoulder"
      ],
      "answer": "forearm",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'colonne vertabrales'?",
      "choices": [
        "spine",
        "hip",
        "belly",
        "chest"
      ],
      "answer": "spine",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for ' apple a day keeps the doctor away'?",
      "choices": [
        "a",
        "an",
        "the",
        "no article"
      ],
      "answer": "an",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'I was tired ___ I went to bed'?",
      "choices": [
        "but",
        "and",
        "because",
        "so"
      ],
      "answer": "so",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'quand'?",
      "choices": [
        "where",
        "when",
        "why",
        "how"
      ],
      "answer": "when",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'coton'?",
      "choices": [
        "cotton",
        "wool",
        "leather",
        "velvet"
      ],
      "answer": "cotton",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'lycee'?",
      "choices": [
        "high school",
        "kindergarten",
        "college",
        "nursery"
      ],
      "answer": "high school",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'not excited'?",
      "choices": [
        "bored",
        "thrilled",
        "glad",
        "hopeful"
      ],
      "answer": "bored",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'relaxed'?",
      "choices": [
        "calm",
        "anxious",
        "scared",
        "sad"
      ],
      "answer": "calm",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'unable to control anger'?",
      "choices": [
        "furious",
        "melancholic",
        "content",
        "hopeful"
      ],
      "answer": "furious",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'oignon'?",
      "choices": [
        "onion",
        "leek",
        "garlic",
        "shallot"
      ],
      "answer": "onion",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'brocoli'?",
      "choices": [
        "broccoli",
        "spinach",
        "lettuce",
        "cabbage"
      ],
      "answer": "broccoli",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'echarpe'?",
      "choices": [
        "scarf",
        "sneakers",
        "boots",
        "slippers"
      ],
      "answer": "scarf",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'eat'?",
      "choices": [
        "eated",
        "ate",
        "eats",
        "eaten"
      ],
      "answer": "ate",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'tableau'?",
      "choices": [
        "board",
        "wall",
        "window",
        "floor"
      ],
      "answer": "board",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'sad'?",
      "choices": [
        "happy",
        "angry",
        "worried",
        "bored"
      ],
      "answer": "happy",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ],
  "intermediate": [
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'citron'?",
      "choices": [
        "lemon",
        "lime",
        "orange",
        "grapefruit"
      ],
      "answer": "lemon",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'p\u00eache'?",
      "choices": [
        "peach",
        "plum",
        "pear",
        "apricot"
      ],
      "answer": "peach",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ananas'?",
      "choices": [
        "pineapple",
        "mango",
        "papaya",
        "orange"
      ],
      "answer": "pineapple",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ananas'?",
      "choices": [
        "pineapple",
        "mango",
        "papaya",
        "orange"
      ],
      "answer": "pineapple",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'concombre'?",
      "choices": [
        "cucumber",
        "zucchini",
        "bean",
        "pea"
      ],
      "answer": "cucumber",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '\u00e9pinard'?",
      "choices": [
        "spinach",
        "lettuce",
        "cabbage",
        "parsley"
      ],
      "answer": "spinach",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'haricot'?",
      "choices": [
        "bean",
        "pea",
        "lentil",
        "corn"
      ],
      "answer": "bean",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pied'?",
      "choices": [
        "foot",
        "toe",
        "heel",
        "leg"
      ],
      "answer": "foot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'jambe'?",
      "choices": [
        "leg",
        "foot",
        "knee",
        "hip"
      ],
      "answer": "leg",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '\u00e9paule'?",
      "choices": [
        "shoulder",
        "chest",
        "neck",
        "arm"
      ],
      "answer": "shoulder",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 't\u00eate'?",
      "choices": [
        "head",
        "shoulder",
        "neck",
        "face"
      ],
      "answer": "head",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'oeil'?",
      "choices": [
        "eye",
        "ear",
        "eyebrow",
        "eyelash"
      ],
      "answer": "eye",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'bras'?",
      "choices": [
        "arm",
        "hand",
        "shoulder",
        "elbow"
      ],
      "answer": "arm",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '____ is your name?'?",
      "choices": [
        "who",
        "what",
        "which",
        "how"
      ],
      "answer": "what",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chien'?",
      "choices": [
        "rabbit",
        "dog",
        "fish",
        "cat"
      ],
      "answer": "dog",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'maison'?",
      "choices": [
        "school",
        "house",
        "store",
        "park"
      ],
      "answer": "house",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'travail'?",
      "choices": [
        "work",
        "play",
        "meeting",
        "break"
      ],
      "answer": "work",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'apprentissage'?",
      "choices": [
        "training",
        "learning",
        "improving",
        "studying"
      ],
      "answer": "learning",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'communication'?",
      "choices": [
        "language",
        "interaction",
        "communication",
        "conversation"
      ],
      "answer": "communication",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pantalon'?",
      "choices": [
        "trousers",
        "shoes",
        "tie",
        "cap"
      ],
      "answer": "trousers",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'veste'?",
      "choices": [
        "jacket",
        "hoodie",
        "sweater",
        "t-shirt"
      ],
      "answer": "jacket",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chaussettes'?",
      "choices": [
        "socks",
        "boots",
        "gloves",
        "shoes"
      ],
      "answer": "socks",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '\u00e9l\u00e8ve'?",
      "choices": [
        "student",
        "teacher",
        "parent",
        "classroom"
      ],
      "answer": "student",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'r\u00e9cr\u00e9ation'?",
      "choices": [
        "recess",
        "breakfast",
        "lesson",
        "exam"
      ],
      "answer": "recess",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'orange'?",
      "choices": [
        "orange",
        "lemon",
        "tangerine",
        "grapefruit"
      ],
      "answer": "orange",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'orange'?",
      "choices": [
        "orange",
        "lemon",
        "tangerine",
        "grapefruit"
      ],
      "answer": "orange",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ananas'?",
      "choices": [
        "pineapple",
        "melon",
        "papaya",
        "mango"
      ],
      "answer": "pineapple",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'banane'?",
      "choices": [
        "banana",
        "pear",
        "grapefruit",
        "orange"
      ],
      "answer": "banana",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'p\u00eache'?",
      "choices": [
        "peach",
        "peech",
        "pech",
        "piche"
      ],
      "answer": "peach",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'banane'?",
      "choices": [
        "banana",
        "bananna",
        "bananah",
        "bannana"
      ],
      "answer": "banana",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chou-fleur'?",
      "choices": [
        "cauliflower",
        "coliflower",
        "couliflower",
        "califlower"
      ],
      "answer": "cauliflower",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'navet'?",
      "choices": [
        "turnip",
        "ternip",
        "tournip",
        "tornip"
      ],
      "answer": "turnip",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ma\u00efs'?",
      "choices": [
        "corn",
        "korn",
        "coorn",
        "corne"
      ],
      "answer": "corn",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'genou'?",
      "choices": [
        "knee",
        "knie",
        "nee",
        "kne"
      ],
      "answer": "knee",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'oreille'?",
      "choices": [
        "ears",
        "eyes",
        "mouth",
        "nose"
      ],
      "answer": "ears",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'crane'?",
      "choices": [
        "skull",
        "scalp",
        "skin",
        "muscle"
      ],
      "answer": "skull",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'poumons'?",
      "choices": [
        "lungs",
        "liver",
        "intestines",
        "kidneys"
      ],
      "answer": "lungs",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'menton'?",
      "choices": [
        "chin",
        "cheek",
        "lip",
        "nose"
      ],
      "answer": "chin",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ventre'?",
      "choices": [
        "belly",
        "chest",
        "back",
        "hip"
      ],
      "answer": "belly",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'hanche'?",
      "choices": [
        "hip",
        "waist",
        "belly",
        "back"
      ],
      "answer": "hip",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'nez'?",
      "choices": [
        "nose",
        "mouth",
        "eye",
        "ear"
      ],
      "answer": "nose",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'cou'?",
      "choices": [
        "neck",
        "chest",
        "back",
        "arm"
      ],
      "answer": "neck",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'menton'?",
      "choices": [
        "chin",
        "nose",
        "lip",
        "neck"
      ],
      "answer": "chin",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'main'?",
      "choices": [
        "hand",
        "foot",
        "elbow",
        "knee"
      ],
      "answer": "hand",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'il part a l'?",
      "choices": [
        "he go to school.",
        "he goes to school.",
        "he going to school.",
        "he gone to school."
      ],
      "answer": "he goes to school.",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'elle as adopte un chien'?",
      "choices": [
        "she adopted an dog.",
        "she adopted a dog.",
        "she adopted dog.",
        "she adopted the dog."
      ],
      "answer": "she adopted a dog.",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'She is smart ___ hardworking.'?",
      "choices": [
        "and",
        "but",
        "or",
        "because"
      ],
      "answer": "and",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'echarpe'?",
      "choices": [
        "scarf",
        "gloves",
        "boots",
        "jeans"
      ],
      "answer": "scarf",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'costume'?",
      "choices": [
        "tuxedo",
        "shorts",
        "t-shirt",
        "jeans"
      ],
      "answer": "tuxedo",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'crayon'?",
      "choices": [
        "pencil",
        "pen",
        "crayon",
        "color"
      ],
      "answer": "pencil",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'devoirs \u00e0 la maison'?",
      "choices": [
        "homework",
        "exam",
        "test",
        "project"
      ],
      "answer": "homework",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'guilty'?",
      "choices": [
        "remorseful",
        "happy",
        "excited",
        "curious"
      ],
      "answer": "remorseful",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'euphoria'?",
      "choices": [
        "intense happiness",
        "deep anger",
        "mild interest",
        "complete boredom"
      ],
      "answer": "intense happiness",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'aubergine'?",
      "choices": [
        "eggplant",
        "carrot",
        "zucchini",
        "lettuce"
      ],
      "answer": "eggplant",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'avocat'?",
      "choices": [
        "avocado",
        "pepper",
        "tomato",
        "cucumber"
      ],
      "answer": "avocado",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'radis'?",
      "choices": [
        "radish",
        "onion",
        "garlic",
        "chili"
      ],
      "answer": "radish",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'concombre'?",
      "choices": [
        "cucumber",
        "zucchini",
        "bean",
        "pepper"
      ],
      "answer": "cucumber",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ongle'?",
      "choices": [
        "fingernail",
        "toe",
        "ankle",
        "eye"
      ],
      "answer": "fingernail",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'coeur'?",
      "choices": [
        "heart",
        "lungs",
        "liver",
        "brain"
      ],
      "answer": "heart",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'coude'?",
      "choices": [
        "elbow",
        "wrist",
        "shoulder",
        "fingers"
      ],
      "answer": "elbow",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'gants'?",
      "choices": [
        "gloves",
        "socks",
        "tie",
        "shirt"
      ],
      "answer": "gloves",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'lunette de soleil'?",
      "choices": [
        "sunglasses",
        "hat",
        "scarf",
        "cap"
      ],
      "answer": "sunglasses",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'examen'?",
      "choices": [
        "exam",
        "homework",
        "recess",
        "essay"
      ],
      "answer": "exam",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'angry'?",
      "choices": [
        "mad",
        "happy",
        "tired",
        "relaxed"
      ],
      "answer": "mad",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'nervous'?",
      "choices": [
        "worried",
        "joyful",
        "calm",
        "bored"
      ],
      "answer": "worried",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for ''?",
      "choices": [
        "staying calm in stress",
        "getting easily frustrated",
        "avoiding emotions",
        "hiding fear"
      ],
      "answer": "staying calm in stress",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ],
  "advanced": [
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'fraise'?",
      "choices": [
        "strawberry",
        "raspberry",
        "blueberry",
        "cherry"
      ],
      "answer": "strawberry",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'past\u00e8que'?",
      "choices": [
        "watermelon",
        "melon",
        "grapefruit",
        "pineapple"
      ],
      "answer": "watermelon",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'banane'?",
      "choices": [
        "banana",
        "peach",
        "plum",
        "grape"
      ],
      "answer": "banana",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'banane'?",
      "choices": [
        "banana",
        "peach",
        "plum",
        "grape"
      ],
      "answer": "banana",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ail'?",
      "choices": [
        "garlic",
        "onion",
        "leek",
        "ginger"
      ],
      "answer": "garlic",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'courgette'?",
      "choices": [
        "zucchini",
        "eggplant",
        "bean",
        "pea"
      ],
      "answer": "zucchini",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'poivron'?",
      "choices": [
        "pepper",
        "tomato",
        "cucumber",
        "zucchini"
      ],
      "answer": "pepper",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'nez'?",
      "choices": [
        "nose",
        "ear",
        "eye",
        "mouth"
      ],
      "answer": "nose",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '\u0153il'?",
      "choices": [
        "eye",
        "ear",
        "mouth",
        "nose"
      ],
      "answer": "eye",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'bouche'?",
      "choices": [
        "mouth",
        "nose",
        "eye",
        "ear"
      ],
      "answer": "mouth",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'oreille'?",
      "choices": [
        "ear",
        "eye",
        "mouth",
        "cheek"
      ],
      "answer": "ear",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'main'?",
      "choices": [
        "hand",
        "arm",
        "foot",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "hand",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'nez'?",
      "choices": [
        "nose",
        "eye",
        "ear",
        "mouth"
      ],
      "answer": "nose",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'jambe'?",
      "choices": [
        "leg",
        "arm",
        "thigh",
        "foot"
      ],
      "answer": "leg",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'genou'?",
      "choices": [
        "knee",
        "leg",
        "foot",
        "toe"
      ],
      "answer": "knee",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '____ did you do that?'?",
      "choices": [
        "why",
        "when",
        "how many",
        "what"
      ],
      "answer": "why",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'bonjour'?",
      "choices": [
        "hello",
        "goodbye",
        "thank you",
        "please"
      ],
      "answer": "hello",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'voiture'?",
      "choices": [
        "bike",
        "bus",
        "car",
        "train"
      ],
      "answer": "car",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'famille'?",
      "choices": [
        "family",
        "friends",
        "team",
        "group"
      ],
      "answer": "family",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'd\u00e9veloppement'?",
      "choices": [
        "growth",
        "building",
        "development",
        "design"
      ],
      "answer": "development",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'compr\u00e9hension'?",
      "choices": [
        "understanding",
        "learning",
        "perception",
        "reflection"
      ],
      "answer": "understanding",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chaussures'?",
      "choices": [
        "shoes",
        "scarf",
        "boots",
        "gloves"
      ],
      "answer": "shoes",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'jupe'?",
      "choices": [
        "skirt",
        "shirt",
        "sock",
        "tie"
      ],
      "answer": "skirt",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'cravate'?",
      "choices": [
        "tie",
        "belt",
        "hat",
        "cap"
      ],
      "answer": "tie",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '\u00e9cole'?",
      "choices": [
        "school",
        "class",
        "student",
        "teacher"
      ],
      "answer": "school",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'livre'?",
      "choices": [
        "book",
        "notebook",
        "pen",
        "paper"
      ],
      "answer": "book",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'happy'?",
      "choices": [
        "joyful",
        "angry",
        "tired",
        "sad"
      ],
      "answer": "joyful",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'scared'?",
      "choices": [
        "afraid",
        "happy",
        "sleepy",
        "calm"
      ],
      "answer": "afraid",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'jealous'?",
      "choices": [
        "envious",
        "tired",
        "glad",
        "shy"
      ],
      "answer": "envious",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'apprehensive'?",
      "choices": [
        "anxious",
        "excited",
        "confident",
        "carefree"
      ],
      "answer": "anxious",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pomme'?",
      "choices": [
        "apple",
        "pear",
        "banana",
        "melon"
      ],
      "answer": "apple",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pomme'?",
      "choices": [
        "apple",
        "pear",
        "banana",
        "melon"
      ],
      "answer": "apple",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for ''?",
      "choices": [
        "watermelon",
        "apple",
        "pear",
        "kiwi"
      ],
      "answer": "watermelon",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'citron'?",
      "choices": [
        "lemon",
        "leemon",
        "lemen",
        "limoon"
      ],
      "answer": "lemon",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'raisin'?",
      "choices": [
        "grape",
        "greip",
        "graip",
        "graep"
      ],
      "answer": "grape",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'poireau'?",
      "choices": [
        "leek",
        "lick",
        "leack",
        "leck"
      ],
      "answer": "leek",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'salade'?",
      "choices": [
        "lettuce",
        "letuce",
        "lattuce",
        "letus"
      ],
      "answer": "lettuce",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'radis'?",
      "choices": [
        "radish",
        "raddish",
        "radissh",
        "raddiche"
      ],
      "answer": "radish",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'bras'?",
      "choices": [
        "arm",
        "leg",
        "head",
        "back"
      ],
      "answer": "arm",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'epaule'?",
      "choices": [
        "shoulder",
        "nose",
        "eyes",
        "lips"
      ],
      "answer": "shoulder",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'pied'?",
      "choices": [
        "foot",
        "hand",
        "elbow",
        "shoulder"
      ],
      "answer": "foot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'doigt'?",
      "choices": [
        "fingers",
        "palms",
        "toes",
        "nails"
      ],
      "answer": "fingers",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'poumons'?",
      "choices": [
        "lungs",
        "nose",
        "ears",
        "eyes"
      ],
      "answer": "lungs",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for '\u00e9paule'?",
      "choices": [
        "shoulder",
        "neck",
        "arm",
        "back"
      ],
      "answer": "shoulder",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'dos'?",
      "choices": [
        "back",
        "shoulder",
        "spine",
        "neck"
      ],
      "answer": "back",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'langue'?",
      "choices": [
        "tongue",
        "mouth",
        "lip",
        "throat"
      ],
      "answer": "tongue",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'oreille'?",
      "choices": [
        "ear",
        "eye",
        "nose",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "ear",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'genou'?",
      "choices": [
        "knee",
        "ankle",
        "thigh",
        "toe"
      ],
      "answer": "knee",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'levre'?",
      "choices": [
        "lip",
        "tongue",
        "cheek",
        "chin"
      ],
      "answer": "lip",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'By the time she arrived, we ____ dinner.'?",
      "choices": [
        "have had",
        "had had",
        "has had",
        "will have"
      ],
      "answer": "had had",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'the'?",
      "choices": [
        "the mount everest is the highest mountain.",
        "mount everest is the highest mountain.",
        "the everest is highest mountain.",
        "everest is highest the mountain."
      ],
      "answer": "mount everest is the highest mountain.",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'parce que'?",
      "choices": [
        "and",
        "but",
        "because",
        "or"
      ],
      "answer": "because",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'menteau'?",
      "choices": [
        "coat",
        "shorts",
        "sandals",
        "cap"
      ],
      "answer": "coat",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'ceinture'?",
      "choices": [
        "belt",
        "scarf",
        "cap",
        "sock"
      ],
      "answer": "belt",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'montre'?",
      "choices": [
        "watch",
        "shirt",
        "pants",
        "sneakers"
      ],
      "answer": "watch",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'salle de classe'?",
      "choices": [
        "classroom",
        "library",
        "gym",
        "cafeteria"
      ],
      "answer": "classroom",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'mathematique'?",
      "choices": [
        "math",
        "history",
        "biology",
        "art"
      ],
      "answer": "math",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'carotte'?",
      "choices": [
        "carrot",
        "beet",
        "radish",
        "pea"
      ],
      "answer": "carrot",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'epinards'?",
      "choices": [
        "spinach",
        "onion",
        "garlic",
        "radish"
      ],
      "answer": "spinach",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'mais'?",
      "choices": [
        "corn",
        "bean",
        "lentil",
        "pea"
      ],
      "answer": "corn",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'chou-fleur'?",
      "choices": [
        "cauliflower",
        "cabbage",
        "broccoli",
        "turnip"
      ],
      "answer": "cauliflower",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'cou'?",
      "choices": [
        "neck",
        "shoulder",
        "back",
        "hip"
      ],
      "answer": "neck",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'go'?",
      "choices": [
        "goed",
        "went",
        "goes",
        "gone"
      ],
      "answer": "went",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'directeur'?",
      "choices": [
        "principal",
        "professor",
        "student",
        "nurse"
      ],
      "answer": "principal",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English word for 'extremely happy'?",
      "choices": [
        "ecstatic",
        "tired",
        "angry",
        "cold"
      ],
      "answer": "ecstatic",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}